helloinsiders.com 2014-11-30

# Privacy Policy | HelloWorld

## HelloWorld, Inc. Privacy Policy

###### Last Revised: January 17, 2013

HelloWorld, Inc. (formerly known as ePrize) is a company that helps other businesses operate sweepstakes, contests, promotions, and loyalty programs ("Promotions"). In addition, HelloWorld occasionally runs its own Promotions. Such Promotions gather personally identifiable information from individuals who choose to enter a particular Promotion and anonymous data regarding the Promotion itself. HelloWorld takes its privacy obligations, both to its clients and to people who enter its Promotions, very seriously. HelloWorld complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. HelloWorld has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program and to view HelloWorld’s certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>.

This policy outlines our treatment of personally identifiable information we collect on behalf of our clients and for our own use. There are three types of Promotions in which HelloWorld is involved and may collect such information: 1) client Promotions; 2) HelloWorld "opt-in" to client Promotions; and 3) HelloWorld Promotions.

### Client Promotions

As a full service promotions and sweepstakes agency, HelloWorld operates Promotions on behalf of its clients. As part of those services, HelloWorld collects personally identifiable information for its clients by use of HelloWorld's proprietary online technology, HelloWorld mailboxes, and points of entry offline. HelloWorld collects such personally identifiable information solely for the use of its clients and the operation of the Promotions. Such uses may include notification of potential winners, fulfillment of prizes, and marketing analysis. HelloWorld strictly limits access to personally identifiable information within its organization. Data is not shared outside of the company except that HelloWorld provides data to our clients, to third parties if directed by our clients, and in response to appropriate governmental or legal requests. Personally identifiable information collected from a client Promotion is never shared with any client other than the client on whose behalf the information was collected. Personally identifiable information collected by HelloWorld on behalf of a client belongs solely to the client and will be used solely in accordance with that client's privacy policy. An individual's desire to "opt-out" of receiving marketing or other information from a client will be handled in accordance with a particular client's privacy policy. HelloWorld requires its clients, by contract, to use the data which HelloWorld collects on its behalf in accordance with generally accepted privacy standards for both offline and online data, which standards call for an "opt-out" method for individuals who have provided personally identifiable information. Ultimately, however, HelloWorld is not responsible for data collected on behalf of clients when such data is in a client's possession.

### HelloWorld “Opt-in” to Client Promotions

From time to time, HelloWorld and a client will agree to allow HelloWorld to offer Promotion entrants an opportunity to "opt-in" to receiving marketing information from HelloWorld and its partners. In such cases, an HelloWorld "opt-in" question will appear on the Promotion registration page clearly explaining to potential entrants that by checking the box they will be agreeing to share their personally identifiable information with HelloWorld. When individuals "opt-in" to receive information from HelloWorld, they are agreeing to receive email and other notices from HelloWorld, including marketing messages, surveys, special offers and notices about other Promotions. Such notices may come from HelloWorld itself, companies with whom HelloWorld has a business relationship, and/or HelloWorld clients. If you want to "opt-out" of receiving such notices from HelloWorld after you have "opted-in", or you wish to correct the information you have provided to HelloWorld, you may do so in one of two ways:

  1. Send an email to [remove@helloworld.com](mailto:remove@helloworld.com). Please make sure to include the name of the Promotion in the subject line and in the body of the email from which you wish to opt-out. Failure to provide this information may delay the processing of your request.
  2. Mail the details of your request to:  
Privacy Policy c/o HelloWorld, Inc.  
One ePrize Drive  
Pleasant Ridge, MI 48069

### HelloWorld Promotions

HelloWorld also runs Promotions on its own behalf. Such Promotions are to generate interest from other businesses in HelloWorld's products and services. HelloWorld uses the personally identifiable information collected in such Promotions as sales leads and may contact the individual registrants by email, mail or phone. HelloWorld will never sell such information or share it with another business. When individuals "opt-in" to receive information from HelloWorld, they are agreeing to receive email and other notices from HelloWorld, including marketing messages, surveys, special offers and notices about other Promotions. Such notices may come from HelloWorld itself or from HelloWorld on behalf of companies with whom HelloWorld has a business relationship. If you want to "opt-out" of being contacted by HelloWorld after you have participated in one of its Promotions, or you wish to correct the information you have provided to HelloWorld, you may do so in one of two ways:

  1. Send an email to [remove@helloworld.com](mailto:remove@helloworld.com). Please make sure to include the name of the Promotion in the subject line and in the body of the email from which you wish to opt-out. Failure to provide this information may delay the processing of your request.
  2. Mail the details of your request to:  
Privacy Policy c/o HelloWorld, Inc.  
One ePrize Drive  
Pleasant Ridge, MI 48069

### HelloWorld's Online Promotion Technology

HelloWorld's proprietary Promotion technology has the ability to collect data other than personally identifiable information for any of the Promotions it operates. HelloWorld may collect information about your computer or device configuration such as your browser type, operating system, or ISP domain name. HelloWorld may collect information about the site you last visited prior to the Promotion or about your activity during your visit to the Promotion site. HelloWorld may also offer social sign-on services that allow you to register for a promotion using a third-party social networking site such as Facebook, Google, or Twitter.  By using these services you allow HelloWorld to access the available information from your third-party social network profile such as your name, age, gender, location, email address, and list of friends.  This information may be used by HelloWorld to administer the technical and operational aspects of the site, and may include using your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server. Your IP address may also be used to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

### Mobile

As a full service promotions and sweepstakes agency, HelloWorld also operates mobile programs on behalf of its clients and itself. As part of those mobile services, HelloWorld collects personally identifiable information by use of HelloWorld's proprietary mobile technology. HelloWorld will not collect personally identifiable information from you without your permission. We treat any information you send to us as non-confidential and non-proprietary and we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any data you submit to us, though we will use reasonable efforts to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data under our control, including physical, electronic and procedural safeguards. HelloWorld respects your privacy. We will only use the information you provide, including your mobile number, to send you content pursuant to the program in which you have requested to participate, though we will share the information we collected from you with the client on whose behalf we collected it. We will not use your information for any other purpose.  HelloWorld is not responsible for information collected on behalf of its clients when such information is in its client's possession. However, we reserve the right at all times to disclose any information as necessary to satisfy any law, regulation, or governmental request; to avoid liability; or to protect our rights or property. When you provide us information in connection with a mobile program, you agree to provide accurate, complete and true information. You agree not to use a false or misleading name or a name that you are not authorized to use. If we, in our sole discretion, believe that any such information is untrue, inaccurate or incomplete, we may prohibit you from further participation in the applicable program and pursue any appropriate legal remedies.  

### Cookies

HelloWorld uses browser cookies in order to improve your user experience by enabling our Promotions to ‘remember’ you or your preferences, either for the duration of your single visit to a website (using "session cookies") or during additional visits ("persistent cookies"). A cookie is a small text file that is stored on your computer or device by a website. Only the visited website will be able to read the contents of a particular cookie. Every cookie is unique to your web browser and contains anonymous information such as a unique identifier, the site name, and some digits and numbers. Cookies serve lots of different purposes like letting you navigate between pages efficiently, storing your preferences or settings, and overall improving your experience with our promotions. Cookies make the interaction between you and HelloWorld Promotions faster and easier. If a website doesn’t use cookies, it will think you are a new visitor every time you move to a new page on the site – for example, when you enter your login details and move to another page it won’t recognize you and it won’t be able to keep you logged in.

Some of our websites will also use cookies or web analytics tracking methods to enable them to target advertising or marketing messages based, for example, on your location and/or browsing habits. Cookies may be set by the website domain you are visiting ("first party cookies") or they may be set by other website domains that run content on the page you are viewing ("third party cookies"). The content of third party cookies can sometimes include Facebook "like" buttons or Twitter "tweet" buttons. 

Some people find the idea of a website storing information on their computer or mobile device intrusive, particularly when that information is stored and used by a third party without their consent. If you do not want to see advertising that has been targeted to your interests or activities, it is possible to block some or all cookies, or even to delete cookies that have already been set, but you might lose some or all of that website's functionality. To manage cookies on your browser please see the articles below:

Internet Explorer: <http://support.microsoft.com/kb/278835> 

Mozilla Firefox: <http://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/cookies-information-websites-store-on-your-computer>

Google Chrome: [http://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=95647](http://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=95647)

Opera: <http://www.opera.com/browser/tutorials/security/privacy/>

### Special Note about Children

Unless otherwise specifically indicated, HelloWorld Promotions are not available to anyone under the age of 13. HelloWorld does, however, operate Promotions on behalf of its clients which collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. In each such instance, HelloWorld and its clients will fully comply with all aspects of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA") in the operation of the Promotion, in the collection of the information itself, and in the subsequent use and deletion of the data collected.

### Your California Privacy Rights (As provided by California Civil Code Section 1798.83)

A California resident who has provided personal information to a business with whom he/she has established a business relationship for personal, family, or household purposes ("California customer") is entitled to request information about whether the business has disclosed personal information to any third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. In general, if the business has made such a disclosure of personal information, upon receipt of a request by a California customer, the business is required to provide a list of all third parties to whom personal information was disclosed in the preceding calendar year, as well as a list of the categories of personal information that were disclosed. However, under the law, a business is not required to provide the above-described lists if the business adopts and discloses to the public (in its privacy policy) a policy of not disclosing customer's personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless the customer first affirmatively agrees to the disclosure. Rather, the business may comply with the law by notifying the customer of his or her right to prevent disclosure of personal information and providing a cost free means to exercise that right.

HelloWorld does not support Do Not Track browser settings and does not currently participate in any Do Not Track frameworks that would allow us to respond to signals or other mechanisms from you regarding the collection of your personal information.

### Contact HelloWorld

If you wish to contact HelloWorld to correct, amend, or delete information (if HelloWorld is holding on to your information as explained above), to communicate about privacy related issues, or for any reason at all, you may do so in one of two ways:

  1. Mail to:  
Privacy Policy c/o HelloWorld, Inc.  
One ePrize Drive Pleasant Ridge, MI 48069; or
  2. Email to: [privacy@helloworld.com](mailto:privacy@helloworld.com)

### Privacy Policy Changes

_HelloWorld may make material changes to this privacy policy from time to time. Therefore, you should periodically visit this page to view the current privacy policy. In the event of a material change to this privacy policy, HelloWorld will send an email advising of the change to all persons whose email addresses we have collected and retained pursuant to the terms set forth above, or by posting notice of the changes on this site._
